<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<IHEActCodeInformation>
<IHEActCodeEntry oid='1.3.6.1.4.1.12559.11.10.1.3.1.42.35' epsosName='epSOSIHEActCode' code='SUBSTCLASS'>
<displayName lang='en'>A qualifier that identifies the class of substance used to treat a patient in an immunization or drug treatment act. The class of substances is expected to be identified using a vocabulary such as NDF-RT, SNOMED CT or other similar vocabulary, and should</displayName>
</IHEActCodeEntry>
<IHEActCodeEntry oid='1.3.6.1.4.1.12559.11.10.1.3.1.42.35' epsosName='epSOSIHEActCode' code='SUBSTANCE'>
<displayName lang='en'>A qualifier that identifies the substance used to treat a patient in an immunization or drug treatment act. The substance is expected to be identified using a vocabulary such as RxNORM, SNOMED CT or other similar vocabulary and should be specific enough </displayName>
</IHEActCodeEntry>
<IHEActCodeEntry oid='1.3.6.1.4.1.12559.11.10.1.3.1.42.35' epsosName='epSOSIHEActCode' code='INTOL'>
<displayName lang='en'>An observation that a patient is somehow intollerant of (e.g., allergic to) a particular substance or class of substances using a specified vocabulary. Use of this vocabulary term requires the use of either the SUBSTANCE or SUBSTCLASS qualifi</displayName>
</IHEActCodeEntry>
<IHEActCodeEntry oid='1.3.6.1.4.1.12559.11.10.1.3.1.42.35' epsosName='epSOSIHEActCode' code='IMMUNIZ'>
<displayName lang='en'>The act of immunization of a patient using a particular substance or class of substances identified using a specified vocabulary. Use of this vocabulary term requires the use of either the SUBSTANCE or SUBSTCLASS qualifier described below, along with an </displayName>
</IHEActCodeEntry>
<IHEActCodeEntry oid='1.3.6.1.4.1.12559.11.10.1.3.1.42.35' epsosName='epSOSIHEActCode' code='DRUG'>
<displayName lang='en'>The act of treating a patient with a particular substance or class of substances identified using a specified vocabulary. Use of this vocabulary term requires the use of either the SUBSTANCE or SUBSTCLASS qualifier described below, along with an identifi</displayName>
</IHEActCodeEntry>
<IHEActCodeEntry oid='1.3.6.1.4.1.12559.11.10.1.3.1.42.35' epsosName='epSOSIHEActCode' code='COMMENT'>
<displayName lang='en'>This is the act of commenting on another act.</displayName>
</IHEActCodeEntry>
<IHEActCodeEntry oid='1.3.6.1.4.1.12559.11.10.1.3.1.42.35' epsosName='epSOSIHEActCode' code='PINSTRUCT'>
<displayName lang='en'>This is the act of providing instructions to a patient regarding the use of medication.</displayName>
</IHEActCodeEntry>
<IHEActCodeEntry oid='1.3.6.1.4.1.12559.11.10.1.3.1.42.35' epsosName='epSOSIHEActCode' code='FINSTRUCT'>
<displayName lang='en'>This is the act of providing instructions to the supplier regarding the fulfillment of the medication order.</displayName>
</IHEActCodeEntry>
</IHEActCodeInformation>
