<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Consent>
	<LegalText>Laonde epSOS Patient Consent?
epSOS does not establish new or specific conditions for collection, processing and storage of  health data. 
epSOS project sets up the mechanism to make health data accessible to health care professionals when the 
patient requires medical service abroad. Thus, epSOS patient's consent is a pre-requisite, not for collecting 
medical data for the purposes of providing medical care in the Point of Care (PoC) by a health care 
professional in a foreign Country, but for the purpose of accessing already existing data in the country of 
residence.
		
Principi de epSOS Patient Consents
The patient should provide the consent for creating his/her epSOS Patient Summary in the residence country 
for access to the summary by a Health Care Provider from abroad (i.e. from epSOS foreign countries). 
The epSOS consent will be a two-step process where the patient gives consent to the creation of the PS in 
her/his home country and is duly informed about potential access to his record by a Health Care Provider in a 
foreign country; as a second step consent to access the Patient Summary in the foreign country s verified in 
this country once the nature of access and purpose is known to the patient. Securing that consent is freely 
given, specific and informed about it..
		
I. The consent will be freely given.  
* The patient has a free choice to participate in the epSOS LSP without any subsequent restrictions or 
  negative influence to receiving all necessary medical treatment or any other medical services if s/he 
  refuses the participation. 
* Patient may withdraw his/her consent at any time.
II. The patient is informed,
* How Date will be used: on your rights and any other circumstances of the processing of your data for the 
  epSOS LSP purposes. 
* consent is free without any consequences if the consent will not be given.
* the collection and further processing of your health data solely for providing medical services is a subject 
  of legislation of a country in which medical care is provided.
	</LegalText>
</Consent>